这里是市民Z在前线情报站北极光营地发回报告
This is Citizen Z here at forward listening post Northern Light
北极光营地
美国国家安全局最后的指挥中心
北极光呼叫威尔逊山
Northern Light to Mount Wilson.
威尔逊山疾控中心 有人吗
Anyone from the Mount Wilson CDC.
我有关于三角洲部队和咬痕组织
I have important information regarding Delta-Xray-Delta
的重要信息
and Operation Bite Mark.
给点力啊 加利福尼亚 坚持住 你们的包裹就在路上
Come on, California. Hang in there. Your package is on the way.
你们只需要去签收一下就好
All you got to do is be there to sign for it.
该死
Gaaaahhh!
这里是威尔逊山 我是海斯廷斯医生
This is Mount Wilson. This is Doctor Hastings at Mount Wilson.
太好了 威尔逊山 这里是北极光营地
Yes! Mount Wilson, you have Northern Light.
我们被一大群第四阶段的感染者们攻击了
We've been attacked by a swarm of level four infected.
我们的防线已经被攻破了
Our defenses have been breached.
逃生通道被高压电围栏封锁着
Our escape has been blocked by a high voltage fence.
从你的位置能进入电力网吗
Can you access the power grid from your location?
不可能 我们到断路器的路上有太多僵尸了
Negative. There are too many Zs between us and the breakers.
好吧 我这边应该可以做些事情
All right. I might be able to do something from my end.
如果我能进入
If I can access anything on
你们实验室的网络 它和外围围栏是由同一个发电机供电的
your lab network powered by the same generator
我会让它超载断电
I might be able to overload it,
切段围栏供电的
knock out power to the fence.
我不知道密码
I don't know the password.
不用担心
Not to worry.
我们是国安局 无所不能
We're the NSA. All of it.
请快点
Please hurry.
好的好的 我
All right. All right. I'm...
我已经进去了
I'm already in.
额 威尔逊山
Uhhh, Mount Wilson.
我们准备执行超载断电了
We are ready to execute overload.
但是
But...
我看到你们的主机
I'm showing your mainframe
和基因测序装置都在同一个网络上
and gene sequencer on the same network.
那意味着你们在那台主机上存储的疫苗文件
That means any vaccine files that you have on that mainframe
都会被毁掉
are likely to be destroyed.
收到请指示
Please advise me.
威尔逊山 我已经准备好超载停电了 请指示
Mount Wilson, I'm ready to execute overload. Please advise.
如果我这么做 我会让你们的工作功亏一篑的
If I do this, I'm going to fry your work.
你们有备份吗
Do you have a backup?
威尔逊山
Mount Wilson?
这儿有太多僵尸了
There's too many!
你必须把我们
You've got to get us
从这里弄出去
out of here now!
该死
Damn it!
就是那样 快 快 快
That's it! Go! Go! Go!
拜托 威尔逊山 坚持住
Come on, Mount Wilson. Hang in there.
塔潘泽大桥
不管你在做什么 别停
Whatever you do, don't stop.
哈哈 你觉得我会吗
Haha, ya think.
躲开
- - Go around!
哈
Ha!
太晚了
Too late!
好技术
Nice driving.
哦 不 不不 不
Oh no. No-no. No!
怎么了
What?
哦 我们没油了
Oh, we're out of gas.
好吧 真有意思
Well that was fun.
哈 哈 没油了
Ha-ha. Out of gas.
弹尽粮绝啊
Running on fumes.
好吧
All right.
你们好像爆胎了
So it looks like you got a flat.
大家小心
Heads up.
有人来了
We got company.
就是这样
That's right.
继续开我们都会活着看到明天的
Keep rolling and we all live to see another day.
好的 我们快点
All right. Let's do this quick.
好的
All right.
好像不是爆胎啊
Doesn't look flat,
但是它不 转了
but it won't... turn.
我们碾过了些有趣的东西
We ran over some fun stuff.
好的 帮我把它弄出来看看怎么回事
Okay. Well help me get it off and let's see what's going on.
难怪车子一直向左偏
Well that explains the pull to the left.
你还在等什么
What are you waiting for?
杀了它 杀了它
Kill it! Kill it!
好了 你 该回老家了
All right, you. Time to go home.
即使在经历了这些事情
Even after all this,
它风景依旧美丽
It's still beautiful.
好好看一眼吧
Take a good look.
可能短时间内不会再回来了
Might be not back for a while.
再见 纽约
So long New York.
来生再见
See ya in the next life.
视频字幕由 SSK字幕组 制作发布
字幕只供学习 请勿做任何商业行为
敬请关注新浪微博@SSK字幕组
僵尸
国度
第一季  第二集
翻译：Cici Windy 慕斯 香蕉奶昔     校对：Jophy
威尔逊山 这里是北极光营地
Mount Wilson, this is Northern Light.
威尔逊山 这是北极光营地
压制：hhjie     时间轴：阿黎     总监：Jophy
快接
Come in.
威尔逊山 这里是市民Z
Mount Wilson, this is Citizen Z.
确认一下你们还在工作
Making sure you're all still in business.
三角洲X光小队
Delta-Xray-Delta.
收到了吗
Do you copy?
有人收到吗
Does anybody copy?
咬痕组织根据地 咬痕组织根据地
Operation Bite Mark. Operation Bite Mark.
您现在收听的是在所有已知的频率上
This is Citizen Z from Camp Northern Light
广播的北极光营地市民Z的直播
broadcasting live on all known frequencies.
即使没有多少人知道
Even a few nobody knows about.
如果你有任何通讯方式 任何方式
If you have any way at all to communicate, any way at all.
如果你有短波 长波 暗波
If you've got short wave, long wave, dark wave,
宽频段 频带
broadband, xband,
传声筒
two cups and a string,
烟幕信号
smoke signals.
任何东西都可以 回应我一下
Anything. Just get back to me.
我有卫星 我会看见的
I've got a satellite. I'll see it.
好吧
All right.
咬痕组织根据地 有人吗
Anyone from Operation Bite Mark.
这里是北极光营地的市民Z
This is Citizen Z from Camp Northern Light.
我有一则关于加利福尼亚情况要向你们汇报更新
I have an update for you on the California situation.
我们得讨论一些可执行的方案
We need to discuss some operational realities.
威尔逊山 收到了吗
Mount Wilson, do you copy?
三角洲X光小队 收到了吗
Delta-Xray-Delta, do you copy?
我不敢相信我跟所有人都失联了
I can't believe I lost everybody.
那是狗拖的雪橇吗
Is that a dog sled?
那是人吗
Is that people?!
我 我觉得那是人类
I... I think it's people!
哦 谢天谢地 有人来了
Oh thank god! Somebody's here!
终于有人来了
Finally.
零食 他们会想要些零食的
Snacks! They're gonna want snacks!
他们 他们会饿的
They're... they'll be hungry.
得去打扫下浴室
Got to clean up the bathroom.
人类
People!
等下 是人还是
Wait. People or...
新泽西州
帕拉默斯公园购物中心
所有这些车
All this cars.
竟然没有一滴油
And not a drop of gas.
偏偏在这种我们以为是最糟糕的情况下 对吧
Just when you thought you saw the worst of it, huh?
他们没有机会了
They didn't stand a chance.
黑色星期五促销吗
Black Friday sale?
你找到汽油了吗
You find any gas?
没 这个地方已经被清空了
No. This area's been picked clean.
什么
What?
你在度假吗
You on vacation?
得有人保持记录
Somebody has to keep record.
你知道我们可能是地球上最后一代人类了
You know we're probably the last generations of humans on earth.
对我们来说这是世界末日 她却觉得是美好回忆
To us it's the apocalypse. To her it's the memories.
要是我踢爆他的蛋蛋会损害到疫苗吗
Would it hurt the antibodies if I kicked him in the nuts?
你叫什么名字 孩子
So what's your name, kid?
一万
Ten Thousand.
那不是个名字 那是个数字
That is not a name. It's a number.
这是我的名字 我自创的
It's my name. Made it up myself.
想必也是
Well I suppose you'd have to.
有什么深意吗
Does it mean anything?
是我要杀的僵尸数量
How many zombies I'm going to kill.
那可是一大波僵尸啊
Well that's a whole lot of zombies.
已经杀掉1055个了
Already on 1,055.
靠
Damn!
杀够一万的时候要怎样
So what happens when you get to 10,000
改名
Change my name.
改成什么 两万吗
To what? Twenty thousand?
杰夫
Jeff.
我喜欢杰夫这个名字
I like the name Jeff.
靠 闭嘴
Ah, shut up.
人都去哪了
Where did everybody go?
除了那两个骑车的人我没看到其他幸存者
I haven't seen a survivor except for those two bikers.
黑色夏天 人都饿死了
Black Summer. Everybody starved to death.
黑色夏天的时候我在费城
I was in Philly for Black Summer.
那时很惨  我足足瘦了三十磅
It was bad. I lost thirty pounds.
还以为自己会死
Thought I was dead.
那你是怎么活下来的
How did you survive?
只要能生存 我无所不作
Did what I had to do.
-嘿
- Hey
别开枪 不是僵尸
Hold on. It's not a Z.
安静点 我没有被咬伤
Peace. No bites here.
百分之百正常活人
100 percent alive.
你那朋友怎么了
What happened to your friend?
发现他有其他缺德朋友
Turns out he had other friends of low morals.
抢走了我的车
Took my ride.
偷人车子 该被枪毙
Horse thieves should be shot.
你该谨慎交友
You should choose better friends.
好主意
Good advice.
我们能帮你什么吗
What can we do for you?
一个人类和平小组能帮到一个单骑行人什么吗
One peaceful group of humans to a lone traveler?
能载我一程吗
Could use a lift.
单独一人可没法在外过夜啊
Sure don't want to spend the night out here alone.
抱歉
Sorry.
我们不是做出租车生意的
We ain't running a taxi service.
你要去哪里
Which way are you headed?
哪里都行 只要不回头就可以
Any direction but back.
听说有一大波僵尸在纽约南边活动
Word is there's a horde on the move south on the New York side.
我瞧见你们在找汽油
I see you're scrounging for gas.
我们常常说 掏钱搭车 没钱滚蛋
You know like we used to say, ass, gas or grass.
就是不能白搭的意思
Nobody rides for free.
我知道在哪可以加满油
I know where you could fill up.
你最好告诉我们在哪里能加油
Now would be the time to share that information.
那地方叫泽西魔鬼冶炼厂 大概五英里开外
Place called Jersey Devil Refinery, maybe five miles off,
下了高速公路就是了
just off the turnpike.
你是怎么知道那有汽油的
How do you know there's gas there?
尸毒爆发的第一天那里就被击溃了
Got overrun day number one.
油罐都是满的
All the tanks are still full,
都放着生锈
just rusting away.
好吧 带我们去冶炼厂
All right, take us to this refinery
如果那儿真如你所说的有汽油的话
And if there's gas there like you say,
你可以搭我们的车去下一个哨站
you can ride with us to the next outpost.
你们不会白跑一趟的
You won't be sorry.
你说对了
You got that right.
我们出发霸
Let's get out of here.
新人 我还有沃伦一辆车
New guy's gonna ride with me and Warren.
其他人上卡车
Everybody else load up in the truck.
是不是以后我们每次停车的时候
So are we just gonna pick
都要捡上这些废物
up every sketchy loser at every place we stop?
我们也把你带上了 不是吗
Well we brought you along, didn't we?
再说了 也没人问过我的意见
Besides, nobody consulted me.
我们不会真的要和这个家伙一起去加州吧
We're not really going to California with this guy, are we?
你知道世界末日就跟戒毒似的 孩子
You know the Apocalypse is a lot like rehab, kid.
过一天算一天吧
Just take it one day at a time,
该干啥就干啥吧
and then do the next indicated thing.
现在这情况 就是要找到更多的汽油
In this case, that means get more gas.
跟着的事 谁知道啊
After that, who knows?
我们死定了
We're doomed.
好吧 如我们所料
Well there you have it.
我们彻底没油了
We're officially on E.
还有多远
How much further?
就在前方
Spittin' distance.
新泽西魔鬼冶炼厂
这可不是冶炼厂
That's not a refinery.
简直就是个僵尸厂
That's a zombie factory.
该死的僵尸
Frackin' zombies.
他们好像迫切地想得到那边的什么东西
They seem to want something in there real bad.
是那个声音
It's that sound.
像蜜蜂闻见了花蜜
Like bees to honey.
或者是僵尸闻见了尸臭
Or Zs to shit.
嘿  你知道这些情况吗
Hey, you know about this?
嘿 反正易得的汽油都没有了
Hey, all the easy gas is gone.
那么大家有什么高见吗
So what's the brilliant plan?
死掉 被吃掉 还是早早回家算了
Die, get eaten, go home early?
这是什么味儿啊
What's that smell?
僵尸臭混合着汽油味
The undead and gasoline.
都是非常易燃
Both highly flammable.
所以绝对不能开火
So no firearms of any kind.
那你想如何处理这个
So how do you want to handle this?
首先我们要让那个声音停下来
Well first we got to shut off whatever's making that noise.
好的 它可能是泵之类的东西
Okay, it's probably some kind of pump.
但在哪
But where?
跟着那些僵尸走
Follow the zombies.
他们貌似都油罐家的最上边去了
They all seem to be headed for the top of that tank.
我们去那儿看看
We'll get up there and check it out.
我们弄个声音把僵尸从油泵那引开
Then we got to have a sound that draws the Zs away from the pump
这样我们就能拿到汽油
so we can get to the gas.
抱歉 我把吉他留在蓝天营地了
Sorry, I left my guitar back at Camp Blue Sky.
汽车喇叭声呢
Car horns?
不行 他们会朝这来
No, they'll all just head this way.
而且所有
And so will every
能听见这声音的僵尸都会被引过来的
other dead head within earshot.
我有个办法
I have something.
僵尸都喜欢高调的声音
Zs like high-pitched sounds.
越悦耳越好
The more musical the better.
哇哦 每天学到新东西啊
Wow, learn something everyday.
好极了
That's great.
你来当诱饵
You're our decoy.
我和她一起
I'll go with her.
我不需要他的帮助
I don't need his help.
不 你需要掩护
No, you need cover.
带着他
Take him.
到架桥顶点时就开始放音乐
And start the music when you get to the top of that catwalk.
你们两个 到另一侧的桥顶上去
You two, get to the top of the other side
看看是否可以停止那个声音 明白了吗
and see if you can kill that noise. Got it.
那个孩子去哪
Where'd that kid go?
他刚才还在这
He was here a minute ago.
哦 他的名字是一万
Oh and his name is Ten Thousand.
他最后能在我们要走时回来
Well he better be back by the time we're ready to go.
嘿 如果我们能让发动那个油罐车 我们就能从那里加油 了
Hey, if we get that tanker started and we could fill it up
那么多的汽油够我们开到加州了
From the main tank, that much gas would get us to California.
我喜欢你这个想法
I like the way you think.
那等下你们都被烧成灰的时候
So what should I be doing
我该做些什么
while you all are getting incinerated to death?
好吧 你带着同志先生
All right, why don't you take Mr. Congeniality here
开着这辆萨博曼退回到安全地带
and the suburban and get back to a safe distance,
以防万一
just in case.
如果 你知道 僵尸来了怎么办
What if... you know... zombies?
如果我们都不幸出了事 那你就带他去加州
If this all ends in tears, you got to get him to California.
好的
Sure.
没问题
No problem.
等一下 伙计 等一下 我会帮你的
Wait one second, buddy. Wait one second. I got you.
我们到了
There you go.
好的 我们来给你暖和一下吧
All right, let's warm you up.
好了 外面很冷 不是吗
Oh yeah, it's cold outside, isn't it?
好了 好孩子 好孩子
Yeah. Good boy. Good boy.
要疯了
You're crazy.
森夏恩 等等我
Sunshine! Hold up!
嘿 慢点
Hey! Slow down!
你会害死我们两的
You're gonna get us both killed.
事实上我们两中只有一个会死
Actually just one of us.
我知道你要做什么
I know what you're trying to do.
没用的
It is not gonna work.
你对我一无所知
You don't know anything about me.
我知道托拜厄斯
I know Tobias
家族的其他人员不会让你走的
and the rest of the family is never gonna let you leave
森夏恩
Sunshine.
我永远都不回去的
Well I'm never going back.
还有 我不是森夏恩
And my name isn't Sunshine.
那个女孩早就死了
That girl died a long time ago.
你不懂
You don't understand.
没有你我回不去
I can't go back without you.
这可不是对家人该有的态度
That's no way to treat family.
艾迪
Addy.
听着  我就是不相信墨菲
Look, I just don't trust Murphy.
好吗 他有点不对劲
Okay? There's something wrong with that dude.
他可不是有点疯而已
He's more than just a little crazy.
整个任务简直就是异想天开
This whole mission is insane.
沃伦和加内特可不这么认为
Warren and Garnett don't think so.
哈蒙德为了保护他而死
Hammond died trying to protect him,
还有很多人都为他牺牲了
and so did a lot of other people.
你也要这样吗
You want to do the same?
不想
No.
但如果这是真的呢
What if it's true?
如果墨菲真的是他们所说的那样
What if Murphy's who they say he is
如果真的有机会制造疫苗呢
and there's a chance for a vaccine?
世界末日已经来临 没救了 艾迪
You don't get a do-over on the end of the world, Addy.
已经太晚了
It's too late.
就算只有一丝机会
If there's the slightest chance
能够唤醒我记忆中的世界
of waking up in the world I remember...
让逝者安息
Where dead things stay dead...
我都要牢牢抓住
That's a chance I'm gonna take.
那就是希望 麦克
Cuz that's hope, Mack.
你知道我已经多久没有那种感觉了吗
You know how long it's been since I've felt something like that?
那不是希望 是谎话
It's not hope. It's a lie.
会害死我们的
And it's gonna get us both killed.
那我宁愿在谎言中死去
Well then I'd rather die believing in a lie
也不愿毫无信念的活着
than live believing in nothing.
你说大道理的时候真他妈性感
Damn, you're sexy when you get all philosophical.
继续转
Keep cranking.
转出来的能量都够供给一座小城市了
Cranking enough to light up a small city.
好了
Here.
试试
Try it.
还来 快点 车快没油了
Okay, hurry up. It's almost running out of gas.
再坚持一会就好
Not for long.
他们一旦停掉了噪音我们就赶紧走
Get ready to go as soon as they kill that noise.
快点 真酷
Come on. That was cool.
是啊 这个坏家伙就是问题所在啊
Yeah. This bad boy's the problem all right.
僵尸最喜欢火和噪音了
Nothing zombies like more than fire and noise.
是啊，还有人脑
Yeah, except brains.
我们要怎么关掉它
How do we turn it off?
制动按钮坏了
Well the stop button doesn't work.
这个肯定是靠压力操作的
Must operate on pressure.
得弄个减压阀之类的东西
Like some kind of relief valve or something.
也许我们可以把它卡主
Maybe we can jam it up.
要不试试用压力或是它排放的任何气体
Well what about the pressure or whatever it's venting?
可以 但我们没时间四处找了
Yeah, we don't hang around to find out.
拿到油就要赶紧跑
Get the gas and get out of dodge.
我们只是需要东西把它卡住
We just need something
像是棍子或者什么的
to jam it up with like a pole or something.
不 我爱这个东西
No! I love this thing.
快想办法
Figure it out!
嘿
Hey,
那些僵尸涌上来
what happened to all the
之后会怎样
zombies that have been coming up here? Huh?
好了
Okay.
他们成功了
They did it.
好了 准备好
All right. Get ready.
好的
Okay.
我们该走了
We should go.
好的
Yeah.
小心
Watch out!
幸好
That was handy.
现在我们知道这些僵尸都怎么了
Now we know what happened to the zombies.
好了 我们真该走了
Okay, it's really time to go.
不知道那边怎么样了
Wonder how it's going?
还没听到什么爆炸声呢
Haven't heard anything blow up.
还没有呢
Yet.
八
Eights.
抓牌吧
Go fish.
动手吧
Do it.
好
Okay.
现在真的该走了
Now it's really time to go.
我在这里 宝贝
Here, boy!
你去哪里了 小家伙
Where'd you go, fella?
我在这呢 宝贝
Here, boy!
你在哪里
Where are you?
快过来 小狗狗
Come here, doggy.
来吧
Come on.
找到你了
There you are.
你还好吗 宝贝 要喝点水吗
How are you, boy? Do you want some water?
渴了吗 好了
Are you thirsty? Yeah.
来这边 喝点水吧
Come here. Let's get some water.
对了
Yeah.
渴了吗
Are you thirsty?
你渴了吗 宝贝
Are you a thirsty boy?
好了
There we go.
对 就是这样 快喝 哥儿们
Yeah, that's right. Drink up, buddy.
快喝
Drink up.
狗狗
Dog!
狗狗 回来
Dog, come back!
狗狗
Dog!
干得漂亮 上面什么情况
Nice job. What was up there?
气压啊 阀门啊 之类的东西
Some kind of a pressure valve thing.
那个池子里全是僵尸 满满的
But that tank is full of zombie goo, like to the top.
真迷人 持续不了多久 同志们
Beautiful. It ain't gonna hold, guys.
放音乐
Start the music!
我们扭起来
Let's dance.
祝我们好运
I'll be damned.
我去拿油管
I got the hose.
拿过来
Here. Give me that.
准备好了吗
You ready?
开始进油
Firing up.
第一次知道钓鱼游戏里也可以出老千
First time I've ever seen anybody cheat at go fish.
这是天赋
It's a gift.
为什么特么要这么久
What the hell is taking so long?
如今的加油服务已经没有当初那么周到了
Full service just ain't what it used to be.
放轻松
Relax.
加内特和沃伦没有问题的
Garnett and Warren know what they're doing.
周围僵尸太多了 我屎都快吓出来了
Too many Zs around here. It's freaking me out.
我有僵尸恐惧症
I got a phobia
自从我被咬了之后
you know ever since I got bit.
我一直想问问你 被咬了之后
I've been meaning to ask you about that. So these bites...
慢着 你算是哪门子医生
Wait. What kind of doctor are you anyway?
我不是真正的医生 更像是业余的药剂师
Not really a doctor, more of an amateur pharmacologist.
那你呢
What about you?
你怎么会成为人类的救星的
How'd you get to be the savior of the human race?
你真的想知道吗
You really wanna know?
真相就是我过去一直被冤枉了
Truth is for a guy who's been wrongly convicted,
其实我充满了正义之感
I'm actually very civic-minded.
我是志愿被实验的
I volunteered.
你们抓错人了 我什么都没做
You got the wrong guy. I didn't do nothin'.
听着 试验证明我不适合啊
Look, I'm being denied my due process, man!
放我走吧
Come on. Let me go.
我是无辜的
I'm innocent, man.
放我走吧
Let me go.
虽然很难 可必须有人这么做
It wasn't easy, but somebody had to do it.
你被选中
You have been selected
成为
for exposure
疫苗实验者
to an experimental...
我天 除非他们狠狠地揍我
Man, they would have to beat me senseless,
把我敲晕
strap me down,
我才可能让他们在我身子里
before I'd ever let anybody inject me
注入新鲜刚出炉的僵尸病毒
with a live zombie virus.
好吧 我不能只为了我自己
Yeah, well it wasn't about me.
有些事你必须去做
You know you do what you got to do.
为了我们的下一代
For the kids...
之后你打了疫苗
So you... you got the vaccine
然后就被咬了
and then you got bitten?
整整八次
Eight times.
哎哟我天
Good God.
是说
If you say so.
那一定很恐怖吧
That must have been horrible.
应该吧
Must have been.
幸运的是我晕过去了 啥都记不起来
Luckily I blacked out, so I don't remember any of it.
不知咋地哈蒙德救了我
Somehow Hammond rescued me.
虽然晚了点 总比没救好 我觉得
Better late than never, I guess.
之后就一直在逃命了
And been on the run ever since.
现在哈蒙德也死了
Now Hammond's dead, too.
是啊 真是美好的时光啊
Yep. Good times.
嘘
Shhh.
我们多了些吵闹的邻居
We got some nosey neighbors.
- 去叫别人 - 别吸引他们
- Call the others! - You're attracting them!
- 我们要出去 - 闭嘴
- Get us out of here! - Shut up!
真棒啊
This is great.
你朋友们的油箱一满
Your friends tank up,
我们就可以把他们的汽油再弄过来
and we take it from them.
可不是我们
There is no we .
我不会回去的
I'm not going back.
死也不会
Not alive.
你为什么要抗拒
Why do you keep fighting this?
你知道他不会放你过你的
You know he's never gonna let you go.
我会想一切办法
I will do whatever I have to do.
你怎么做
You'll do what?!
去告诉你的新朋友们我是谁
Tell your new friends who I am?
如果我告诉他们你是谁 会怎么样
What happens when I tell them what you are?!
不 神啊
No! God!
我勒个去啊 伙计
Good grief, dude
墨菲 没事的
Murphy, all right.
墨菲 墨菲
Murphy. Murphy.
看着我
Look at me.
看着我的眼睛
In my eyes.
你在这里很安全
You're safe in here man.
他们进不来的
They can't get you.
现在你保持冷静就可以
Now just try to breathe through it, man.
呼吸
Breathe.
他们就在那儿
Right there. Right there.
好吧 够了 听着 外面就两个
All right, that's enough. Look, there's only two of them.
听着伙计 我现在要出去
Look man, I'm gonna go out there.
把他们赶跑
I'm gonna draw them away
让他们尝尝我的厉害
and I'm gonna mercy them.
现在你只要冷静一点
Now you just... just chill out.
为啥事情都这么麻烦
Why is nothing ever easy?
好了 跟我来 小家伙们
Okay, follow me boys!
来啊
Come on!
新鲜的肉
Fresh meat.
哦 好家伙
Oh, nice guy.
你感觉到了吗
Did you feel that?
注意听
Listen.
到车子里去
Get in the truck!
快
Come on!
哦 嘿 孩子 嘿
Oh. Hey, boy! Hey!
该死
Damn it.
嘿 蠢货
Hey, stupid!
他不好吃
You don't want him.
他味道不咋地
He's all chewed up already.
来啊 朋友 过来
Come on, friend. Come on.
抬起下巴 让医生来检查下子
Raise your chin for your ol' pal Doc.
别慌 墨菲 他们进不去的
Hang in there, Murphy! They can't get you!
第1058个
One thousand fifty eight.
把他们弄走
Get them off!
第1059个
One thousand fifty nine.
第1060个 射得漂亮 孩子
One thousand sixty! Nice shot, kid!
墨菲
Murphy!
嘿 罗伯塔
Hey, Roberta.
这该死的油管我拿不下来
I can't get this damn hose off.
我们要走了
We got to get going.
下去 下去
Get off! Get off!
下去
Get off!
那个是墨菲吗
Is that Murphy?
真是不幸啊 还真是他
Unfortunately, yes.
我们走 我们走
Get out of here. Get out of here! Go!
快点
Come on!
慢着 你要干什么
Wait a minute. What are you gonna do?
我要去救墨菲 快 快走
I got to save Murphy. Come on. Get out of here.
滚开 特拉维斯
Get out of my way, Travis.
我不想杀你
I don't want to have to kill you.
没有问题
That's not gonna be a problem.
该回家了 森夏恩
It's time to go home, Sunshine.
想都别想
You forget.
我逃惯了
I'm used to it.
懦夫
Coward!
该死
Shit!
不要
No!
不
放开他 混蛋
Get off of him you bastard!
嘿
Hey!
停下
Stop!
不许你碰这一年来
You're not gonna kill the only living thing
我见到的唯一生物
I've seen in a year!
快 你快出来
- - Come on! Got to get out of here.
不 外面僵尸太多了 我不出去
No! There's too many! I can't!
快出来
Come on!
你不明白
You don't understand!
我不出去 不能出去
I can't. I can't.
我动不了
I can't.
可以的 现在不是害怕的时候
Yes! It is not the time!
不 不 我不出去
No! No! I can't!
车子马上就要爆炸了
This is gonna explode!
你不明白
You don't understand!
我动不了
I can't!
电影里都是一下就打晕了
This works easier in the movies.
第1062个
One thousand sixty two.
快走
Come on.
我还活着
I'm alive?
嘿
Hey.
你 你还活着 不可能
You're... You're still alive. No way.
你还活着
You're still alive.
我还活着
I'm still alive.
好棒 尝到我的厉害了吧 疯狗
Yeah! Yeah, take that Cujo!
就是要这个样子
That's what I'm talkin' about!
我们做到了 小狗狗 我和你 我们做到了
We did it, pup. Me and you, we did it.
我们还活着
We're alive.
就你和我 小狗狗 就你和我
It's just you and me, pup. Just you and me.
好的 我找到了牛肉饼和牛肉三明治
Okay, I've got beef patty and sloppy joe.
看起来你比较喜欢吃牛肉
You look like a beef eater to me.
好的
Okay.
开饭啦
Here we go.
这其实是我经历过的最棒的约会了
This is actually one of the best first dates I've ever had.
开饭喽 看起来很好吃吧
Here we go. Oh yeah, doesn't that look good?
喔 慢慢吃 伙计
Whoa. Slow down, dude.
我只有十年的库存
I only have ten year supply.
伙计
Dude?
嗯 这不是个好名字 是吧
Hmmm. That's not a very good name, is it?
我们可以想个更好的 那个伙计 怎么样
Nah, we can do better than that, can't we? What about 'the dude?'
我真的很喜欢 那个伙计 这部电影
I really like that movie.
不喜欢 好吧 我们还可以想个更好的
No? Yeah, we can come up with something better than that.
好的 好小子
Yes. Good boy.
那是什么
What is that?
看起来有人在玩儿火呀
Looks like somebody's been playing with matches.
那里是什么 炼油厂
What is that? Is that a refinery?
我们找到汽油了吗
So did we get the gas?
真不错 谁搞砸了
Great. Who screwed that up?
哦 不好意思
Oh. Sorry.
那么 你的朋友在哪儿
So where's your friend?
他死了 而且他不是我的朋友
He didn't make it. And he wasn't my friend.
哈罗
Hello?
哈罗 是我 北极光营地的市民Z
Hello. It's me, Citizen Z from Northern Light.
请问你是
To whom am I speaking?
查理加内特警官
Sergeant Charlie Garnett.
太棒了
Excellent.
很高兴能和你说话 长官
Good talking to you again sir.
你那儿怎么样
How's it going?
马马虎虎
It's going.
好的 那个包裹怎样呢
Excellent. And the package?
还活着
Still alive.
请告诉我把他带到哪儿去
Please tell us where to drop him off.
加州
California.
加州 等等 不行
California? Wait. No.
慢着 那是不可能的
Hold on. That's not gonna happen.
我们要去更近的地方
We need to go some place closer.
更近 额
Closer? Uh...
抱歉 警官 不能再近了
Sorry Sergeant, but there is no... closer.
我们和管事儿的说话吗
Can I speak to someone in charge?
好的 收到 我确定他们也很想跟你说话
Yeah, copy that. I'm sure they'd like to talk to you too.
但有点困难
But that may be a little problematic.
有点困难是什么意思
What do you mean problematic?
一大波僵尸正在靠近
More puppies and kittens.
为什么不能和实验室的人说话
Why can't I speak to somebody at the lab?
好吧长官
Well, sir.
到底怎么了
What's going on?!
我们失联了
We've lost contact.
那他们还活着吗
Are they even still alive?
我正在努力确认中 长官
I'm working on confirming that, sir.
我在屏幕上看到一大波僵尸正在向你们靠近
I've got a screen full of incoming Zs headed your way.
你最好采取行动了 军士
You'd better get moving, Sergeant.
我能找到你 但现在 一直往西走到海边
I'll find you. But for now, go west till you hit the ocean.
哈罗
Hello?
加内特警官
Sergeant Garnett?
警官
Sergeant?
我知道
I know.
我知道 可他们是咱们的唯一希望了
I know. But they're the only chance we got.
我要来电音乐
I need some music.
我们可以的 好小子
Yeah, we can. Yeah, that's a good boy.
看
Look.
帅呆了
Awesome.
我以为再也见不到这玩意儿了
Never thought I would see this thing again.
等等 小孩儿来了
Wait! Here comes the kid!
我找到这个
Found these.
小家伙
Kid.
你简直是上帝
You're a god.
好的 我们要抓紧了
Yeah well hurry up.
打扰一下 女士
Excuse me, ma'am.
你头发里有根手指
You have a finger in your hair.